Guide to the Cornell University Board of Trustees records, 1865-2001.
Cornell University Board of Trustees records
- Series II. Executive Committee
  - Subseries Ia. Working Files
    - Working file, 1891-01 - 1891-02 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      Includes note from Thurston regarding poor water on campus, letter from George Warner regarding dangerous water in Cascadilla dorm
    - Working file, 1891-03 - 1891-04 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      Includes sketched plan of central campus, Lincoln Hall inscription written by AD White
    - Working file, 1891-05 - 1891-06 (Box 27, Folder 27)
      Includes report on the Department of Political Economy and Finance, Memorandum concerning organization of the Library
    - Working file, 1891-06 - 1891-07 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      Includes report from Sibley on arson of zoology building, diagrams and details of refitting McGraw departments and museum
    - Working file, 1891-07 - 1891-09 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      Includes plan of University lighting
    - Working file, 1891-10 - 1891-12 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Working file, 1892-01 - 1892-09 (Box 27, Folder 31-35)
    - Working file, 1892-09 - 1892-10 (Box 27, Folder 36)
      Includes letter from faculty petitioning for school house (with sketch of land
    - Working file, 1892-11 - 1892-12 (Box 27, Folder 37)
      Includes letter from Ithaca Street Railway about extension of tracks
    - Working file, 1893-01 - 1893-04 (Box 27, Folder 38)
      Includes museum budget breakdown including cast purchases
    - Working file, 1893-04 - 1893-09 (Box 27, Folder 39-40)
    - Working file, 1893-09 - 1893-12 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - Working file, 1894-01 - 1894-02 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Working file, 1894-03 - 1894-04 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Includes report from the Sanitation Committee on faculty rooms, sketch of proposed walkway
    - Working file, 1894-05 - 1894-06 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Includes list of band instruments wanted
    - Working file, 1894-07 - 1894-12 (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
    - Working file, 1895-01 - 1895-02 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Includes detailed letter of Cornell milk production, memorandum of establishing a quarterly review of history
    - Working file, 1895-03 - 1895-06 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
    - Working file, 1895-07 - 1895-09 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      Includes estimates and lists for new Veterinary College
    - Working file, 1895-10 - 1895-12 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      Includes letter from E.A. Fuertes requesting renovations and updates to the observatory, petition from women to receive fencing instruction
    - Working file, 1896-01 - 1896-02 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Working file, 1896-03 - 1896-04 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      Includes list and description of apparatus contributed for the New York Electrical Exposition
    - Working file, 1896-05 - 1896-06 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      Includes letter from the Christian Association for land (with map)
    - Working file, 1896-07 - 1896-09 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      Includes petition from faculty against the location of the veterinary buildings and the health hazards, with a response from the faculty who support the buildings
    - Working file, 1896-10 - 1896-12 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Working file, 1897-01 - 1897-10 (Box 28, Folder 18-22)
    - Working file, 1897-11 - 1897-12 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      Includes letter from Burt Green Wilder on the inspection of the G.B. Sutton bird donation
    - Working file, 1898-01 - 1898-02 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      Includes Library Council action of extending hours and borrowing times
    - Working file, 1898-03 - 1898-04 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Working file, 1898-05 (Box 28, Folder 26)
      Includes the petition of Howard Cobb vs. Cornell, conditions of Veterinary College
    - Working file, 1898-06 (Box 28, Folder 27)
      Includes letter from paleontology department about collections including US map listing geographic locations not represented in the collections, Gilbert Harris' description of fossil collection
    - Working file, 1898-07 - 1898-09 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Working file, 1898-10 (Box 28, Folder 29)
      Includes copy of Medical Council minutes
    - Working file, 1898-11 - 1898-12 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Includes report that cases of typhoid on campus were not linked to university conditions or Ithaca water supplies, sketch of proposed changes in basement of Lincoln Hall,
    - Working file, 1899-01 - 1899-02 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Working file, 1899-03 - 1899-04 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Includes plan for the business management of the State College of Forestry, report on fire protection and water pumping
    - Working file, 1899-05 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Includes report on the Medical Course, request from Ellen Canfield to allow rowing on Triphammer Pond, general rules for the library
    - Working file, 1899-06 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Includes Alpha Delta Phi request for land lease and sketched map, sketch of Reservoir Ave. map
    - Working file, 1899-07 - 1899-08 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Includes Frank William Padgham scholarship information
    - Working file, 1899-09 - 1899-10 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Working file, 1899-11 - 1899-12 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Includes Prof. Henry's petition to create a center for the College of Agriculture with signatures, newspaper clippings
    - Working file, 1900 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      Includes reports of the conditions of the infirmary, statements from doctors and patients regarding the Delta Chi fire
    - Working file, 1900-01 - 1900-03 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      Includes petition to keep armory open until 9 signed by basketball team, list of materials for the Paris Exhibition
    - Working file, 1900-04 - 1900-07 (Box 29, Folder 11-13)
    - Working file, 1900-08 - 1900-09 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      Includes map of proposed foot bridge over Fall Creek
    - Working file, 1900-10 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      Includes report of the measurements of flow of Fall Creek made at the hydraulic lab
    - Working file, 1900-11 - 1900-12 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      Includes trade-mark statements and declarations for Laurence McCormick's "Cornell University Special Blend Whisky" with logo
    - Working file, 1901-01 - 1901-04 (Box 29, Folder 17-18)
    - Working file, 1901-05 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      Includes correspondence from J. D. Rockefeller Jr. regarding donation
    - Working file, 1901-06 - 1901-07 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      Includes information on the proposed water power central electric light and power plant, correspondence regarding Rockefeller donation
    - Working file, 1901-08 - 1901-10 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      Includes Forestry Council minutes
    - Working file, 1901-11 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      Includes report of the Land Committee, letter from E. Hitchcock regarding the conditions of the gymnasium and the spread of communicable diseases
    - Working file, 1901-12 (Box 29, Folder 23)
      Includes reports of damage to the Hydraulic Laboratory due to flooding
    - Working file, 1902-01 - 1902-02 (Box 29, Folder 24)
      Includes appointment of Martha VanRensselaer
    - Working file, 1902-03 - 1902-04 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Working file, 1902-05 (Box 29, Folder 26)
      Includes correspondence regarding change in cadet uniforms
    - Working file, 1902-06 - 1902-10 (Box 29, Folder 27-29)
    - Working file, 1902-10 - 1902-11 (Box 29, Folder 30)
      Includes letter from Cuba's first president, Tomas Estrada Palma, about the scholarship for Antonio Maceo Jr.; report of the Land Committee; letter regarding the proposed toboggan slide
    - Working file, 1902-12 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Working file, 1903-01 - 1903-02 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence on "The Physical Review", newspaper clipping and correspondence on appeal of Mexico and China regarding coinage, petition from students and resolutions asking for clean drinking water
    - Working file, 1903-02 - 1903-04 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Includes copy of the final report on the typhoid epidemic with notes, copy of the letter from Schurman and resolutions regarding Carnegie paying for student bills, McClure's article, correspondence from Ithaca Water Works about filtration plant
    - Working file, 1903-05 - 1903-06 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Includes petitions and correspondence regarding the closing of the Forestry school
    - Working file, 1903-06 - 1903-07 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Includes pamphlet on the Professorial Pension Fund, specifications for modifications of water filtration plant
    - Working file, 1903-08 - 1903-09 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Includes letter from Professor Jenks asking for leave of absence with copy of Theodore Roosevelt's request
    - Working file, 1903-10 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Includes R. Thurston recommending names for Sibley Dome, condition of the Sage Chapel organ, report of the Land Committee, general rules for the library,
    - Working file, 1903-11 - 1903-12 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Working file, 1904-01 - 1904-02 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Includes proposal and specifications for electric elevator in Rockefeller Hall
    - Working file, 1904-03 - 1904-04 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Includes correspondence on worsening condition of Sage organ
    - Working file, 1904-05 - 1904-06 (Box 30, Folder 10-11)
    - Working file, 1904-07 - 1904-09 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      Includes study of campus houses (Fuertes, Thurston) by Van Pelt, memorandum regarding location of State College of Agriculture
    - Working file, 1904-10 - 1904-11 (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
    - Working file, 1905-01 - 1905-02 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      Includes conditions of water in Eddy Pond
    - Working file, 1905-03 - 1905-04 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      Includes correspondence on the transport of the Petrarch and Icelandic collections with agreement between Cornell and the librarian of the Royal Mediceo Laurentian Library of Florence, recommendation for parking on Stewart Avenue, Petition from female students against the resignation of the Sage College Warden
    - Working file, 1905-05 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      Includes letter from the War Department asking Cornell to admit 12 additional Filipino students
    - Working file, 1905-06 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      Includes protests against election of Earl Lovell as director of College of Civil Engineering, report of the President White School of History and Political Science, report of the Committee on Exhibit of Cornell at the Louisiana Purchase Exposition
    - Working file, 1905-06 - 1905-10 (Box 30, Folder 19-20)
    - Working file, 1905-11 - 1905-12 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      Includes information on the travelling summer school of agriculture
    - Working file, 1906-01 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      Includes requisition for Ordnance and Ordnance stores for use of battalion cadets
    - Working file, 1906-02 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Working file, 1906-03 - 1906-04 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      Includes report on three cases of typhoid, minutes of a meeting of the Cornell Association of Class Secretaries
    - Working file, 1906-05 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Includes ground floor plan of room assignments in Goldwin Smith, correspondence regarding trolley installation, report on fraternity houses on Cornell property, report on conditions of Medical College buildings
    - Working file, 1906-06 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Working file, 1906-06 - 1906-10 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Includes complaint from botany department about dogs on campus rolling in flower beds and killing squirrels, large student petition to permit Henry Gillette to sell papers and chocolate on campus, Ralph S. Tarr requesting a wet laboratory for geography, correspondence on Jamestown Exposition
    - Working file, 1906-11 - 1906-12 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Includes correspondence on the Ten Year Book, map of Ithaca with proposed additional telephone line, report of Chi Psi fire
    - Working file, 1906-12 - 1907-01 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Includes report on Barnes Hall, request for skating and tobogganing on Beebe Lake, informal report regarding fire protection on campus, correspondence on bronze statue of Ezra Cornell
    - Working file, 1907-02 - 1907-03 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Includes reports on fire protection, professor Hull's request for a collection of American Historical Manuscripts, correspondence concerning Fayerweather's tomb, report on Scarlet Fever quarantine, report of the committee on request to raise age of admission for female students,
    - Working file, 1907-04 - 1907-05 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Working file, 1907-06 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      Includes documents concerning affiliation with New York College of Dentistry
    - Working file, 1907-07 - 1907-08 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      Includes request for seismograph for Cornell
    - Working file, 1907-09 - 1907-10 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      Includes proposed sketch of gymnasium annex
    - Working file, 1907-11 - 1907-12 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      Includes report of surface drainage with map, map with lamp locations
    - Working file, 1908-01 - 1908-02 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      Includes memorandum and correspondence in connection with HH Lannigan claim
    - Working file, 1908-03 - 1908-06 (Box 31, Folder 13-15)
    - Working file, 1908-07 - 1908-09 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      Includes letter regarding scholarships for Indian students, letter from the Society for the Advancement of India, letter from the War Department requesting free tuition for five Filipino students
    - Working file, 1908-10 - 1908-12 (Box 31, Folder 17-18)
    - Working file, 1909-01 - 1909-02 (Box 31, Folder 19-20)
    - Working file, 1909-03 - 1909-04 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      Includes plans and specifications for arboretum, request for new entrance to Sheldon Court (with photograph postcard), request for an exhibit from Gargoyle,
    - Working file, 1909-05 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      Includes report from faculty on comparative length of term time in leading American universities
    - Working file, 1909-06 - 1909-08 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - Working file, 1909-09 - 1909-10 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Includes printed pamphlet on missionary work at Beulah Chapel Shanghai, correspondence on Filipino students from the War Department
    - Working file, 1909-11 - 1909-12 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Includes proposal of alterations to Carnegie Filter Plant
    - Working file, 1910-01 - 1910-02 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Working file, 1910-03 - 1910-04 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Includes International Commission on the Teaching of Mathematics second preliminary report, Comstock Memorial Library fund, complaint about dog attack in the library
    - Working file, 1910-05 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Includes correspondence and petition on military uniforms, sample of certificate of proficiency in Military Science and Tactics
    - Working file, 1910-06 - 1910-07 (Box 32, Folder 8-9)
      Includes correspondence from War Department on Filipino students, correspondence on military uniforms
    - Working file, 1910-08 - 1910-10 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Includes sketch of Wait and Thurston Ave plots, reports on the elm leaf beetle damage, reorganization of Sage College and appointment of matron, correspondence on Filipino and Chinese students
    - Working file, 1910-11 - 1910-12 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      Includes correspondence from War Department on Filipino students, letter regarding women's physical training appropriation
    - Working file, 1911-01 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Working file, 1911-02 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      Includes proposal for women's dormitory
    - Working file, 1911-03 - 1911-04 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      Includes special report on cadet uniforms and correspondence
    - Working file, 1911-05 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      Includes letter from Ralph Tarr on the importance of an experimental laboratory for studying glacial movement, correspondence on regulation of motor vehicles, report of the Committee on Synchronized Clocks
    - Working file, 1911-06 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Working file, 1911-07 - 1911-08 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      Includes correspondence from War Department on Filipino Students
    - Working file, 1911-09 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      Includes letter from Cornell Women of Washington regarding the Dean of Women position
    - Working file, 1911-10 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Working file, 1911-11 - 1911-12 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      Includes correspondence on free tuition for Filipino and Japanese students
    - Working file, 1912-01 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1912-02 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Includes basic list of materials in Goldwin Smith Collection, building sketch,
    - Working file, 1912-03 - 1912-04 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Working file, 1912-05 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Includes signed petition from Cornell women in support of the Adviser of Women
    - Working file, 1912-06 - 1912-10 (Box 33, Folder 5-7)
    - Working file, 1912-11 - 1912-12 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Includes correspondence from Corda Fratres, donation for eugenics lectures
    - Working file, 1913-01 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Working file, 1913-02 - 1913-03 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      Includes letter from Navy Department regarding summer training courses
    - Working file, 1913-04 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Working file, 1913-05 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      Includes petition against rising costs of living from Cornell women
    - Working file, 1913-06 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Working file, 1913-07 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Working file, 1913-08 - 1913-09 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      Includes correspondence on Chinese scholarships
    - Working file, 1913-10 - 1913-12 (Box 33, Folder 16-17)
      Includes petitions of female graduate students on housing
    - Working file, 1914-01 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      Includes
    - Working file, 1914-02 - 1914-03 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Working file, 1914-04 - 1914-05 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Working file, 1914-06 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      Includes New York State sealed act for Agricultural Cooperative Extension
    - Working file, 1914-07 - 1914-08 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Working file, 1914-09 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      Includes Ithaca Traction Corp. proposed switch line
    - Working file, 1914-10 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      Includes letters from Chinese and Filipino students
    - Working file, 1914-11 - 1914-12 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      Includes recommendations for improving Military Department, petition for bridge over Cascadilla
    - Working file, 1880 - 1904 (Box 33, Folder 26)
      Undated material includes sketch of bridge, sketch of alumni hall office layout, Toner Library paper seal,
    - Working file, 1915-01 - 1915-04 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Working file, 1939-11 - 1939-12 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1940-01 - 1940-04 (Box 34, Folder 2-4)
      llenroc facts with Delta Phi
    - Working file, 1940-05 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Includes recommendations on immunizations
    - Working file, 1940-06 - 1940-12 (Box 34, Folder 6-11)
    - Working file, 1941-01 - 1941-09 (Box 34, Folder 12-18)
    - Working file, 1941-10 - 1941-12 (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
    - Mail Vote, 1942-01 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Working file, 1942-01 - 1942-08 (Box 35, Folder 4-9)
    - Working file, 1942-09 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      Includes request of leave of absence for Hans Bethe to go to MIT
    - Working file, 1942-10 - 1942-12 (Box 35, Folder 11-14)
    - Working file, 1943-01 - 1943-03 (Box 35, Folder 15-16)
    - Working file, 1943-04 - 1943-12 (Box 36, Folder 1-7)
    - Working file, 1944-01 - 1944-12 (Box 36, Folder 8-16)
    - Working file, 1945-01 - 1945-02 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1945-03 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      Letter about Flemish tapestry purchased for Jennie McGraw Fiske from Prince Demidoff and Princess Mathilde, designed by Karel von Mander, woven on border "mander fecit AD 1619. 14 ft high, thirteen wide
    - Working file, 1945-04 - 1945-12 (Box 37, Folder 3-9)
    - Working file, 1946-01 - 1946-09 (Box 37, Folder 10-17)
    - Working file, 1946-08 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1946-09 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      Includes the South Hill Faculty Housing Project report (includes photographs)
    - Working file, 1946-10 - 1946-12 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
    - Working file, 1947-01 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Working file, 1947-02 - 1947-03 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      Includes signed petition to change status of ROTC to elective rather than compulsory
    - Working file, 1947-04 - 1947-06 (Box 38, Folder 7-10)
    - Working file, 1947-07 - 1947-12 (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
    - Working file, 1948-01 - 1948-07 (Box 39, Folder 6-11)
    - 1948-08 - 1948-12 (Box 40, Folder 1-5)
    - Working file, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 6-12)
      MAR Charles Manning, Proctor, resigned for impersonating officer and given six month sentence
    - Working file, 1950-01 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      Includes proposal for building Anabel Taylor Hall War Memorial and Interfaith building
    - Working file, 1950-02 - 1950-09 (Box 40, Folder 14-19)
    - Working file, 1950-10 - 1950-12 (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
    - Working file, 1951-01 - 1951-03 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
    - Working file, 1951-04 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Includes document regarding burial rights in the crypt of Sage Chapel
    - Working file, 1951-05 - 1951-12 (Box 41, Folder 7-10)
    - Working file, 1952-01 - 1952-04 (Box 41, Folder 11-13)
    - Working file, 1952-05 - 1952-06 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      Includes recommendations for purchase of Sapsucker Woods
    - Working file, 1952-07 - 1952-12 (Box 41, Folder 15-17)
    - Working file, 1953-01 - 1953-04 (Box 41, Folder 18-20)
    - Working file, 1953-05 - 1953-12 (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
    - Working file, 1954-01 - 1954-12 (Box 42, Folder 5-11)
    - Working file, 1955-01 - 1955-09 (Box 42, Folder 12-17)
    - Working file, 1955-10 - 1955-12 (Box 43, Folder 1-5)
    - Working file, 1956-01 - 1956-12 (Box 43, Folder 6-17)
    - Working file, 1957-01 - 1957-06 (Box 43, Folder 18-24)
    - Working file, 1957-07 - 1957-12 (Box 44, Folder 1-4)
    - Working file, 1958-01 - 1958-12 (Box 44, Folder 5-6)
    - Working file, 1958-02 - (Box 44, Folder 7)
      Includes University Library expansion report and copy of renderings
    - Working file, 1958-03 - 1958-09 (Box 44, Folder 8-13)
    - Working file, 1958-10 (Box 44, Folder 14-15)
      Includes proposed gift of Herbert F Johnson
    - Working file, 1958-11 - 1958-12 (Box 44, Folder 16-17)
    - Working file, 1959-01 - 1959-08 (Box 44, Folder 18-24)
    - Working file, 1959-09 - 1959-12 (Box 45, Folder 1-4)
    - Working file, 1960-01 - 1960-12 (Box 45, Folder 5-16)
    - Working file, 1961-01 - 1961-05 (Box 46, Folder 1-7)
    - Working file, 1961-06 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      Includes proofs of university brochure
    - Working file, 1961-08 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      Includes minutes of the Centennial Planning Committee
    - Working file, 1961-09 - 1961-12 (Box 46, Folder 10-14)
    - Working file, 1962-01 - 1962-02 (Box 46, Folder 15-17)
    - Working file, 1962-03 - 1962-12 (Box 47, Folder 1-10)
    - Working file, 1963-01 - 1963-02 (Box 47, Folder 11-12)
    - Working file, 1963-03 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Working file, 1963-04 - 1963-05 (Box 47, Folder 14-15)
    - Working file, 1963-06 - 1963-12 (Box 48, Folder 1-5)
    - Working file, 1964-01 - 1964-06 (Box 48, Folder 6-11)
    - Working file, 1964-07 - 1964-12 (Box 49, Folder 1-4)
    - Working file, 1965-01 - 1965-06 (Box 49, Folder 5-10)
    - Working file, 1965-07 - 1965-12 (Box 50, Folder 1-5)
    - Working file, 1966-01 - 1966-05 (Box 50, Folder 6-11)
    - Working file, 1966-06 - 1966-09 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - Working file, 1966-06 - 1966-09 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Orientation meeting, 1966-09 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Working file, 1966-10 - 1966-12 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Working file, 1966-10 - 1966-12 (Box 51, Folder 6-7)
    - Working file, 1967-01 - 1967-05 (Box 51, Folder 8-12)
    - Working file, 1967-06 (Box 59, Folder 1)